Check my CV in HTML:

https://adolpholg.github.io/curr culum.github.io/

Contact

Herzliya, Israel

adolpholg@icloud.com

+972 55-2577525

Main competences

Customer Service
Leadership
Problem Solving
Negotiation
Teamwork
Selenium
Microsoft SQL Server
HTML
CSS
Java

Languages

Hebrew (Fluent)

Portuguese (Native)

Spanish (Fluent)

English (Fluent)

Certifications

QA Software Tester

People Management

Sales Techniques

Basic Human Resources

Basic Finance for Entrepreneurs

Adolpho Liberman

Israel

Hello! My name is Adolpho Liberman, I'm 25 years old, I'm Brazilian and I've lived in Israel for 4 years. I came to Israel so I could enlist in the army, and now that I've finished my military service, I've been able to go back to study and work normally like before the army. I have just graduated from the Web and Mobile QA course at Technion University. I'm a hardcore gamer, traveler, tech savvy, good with people, communicative and responsible.

Military Service

Paratroopers Brigade (2019 - 2021)

Commander and fighter in the 890th Battalion, released with honors in the rank of sergeant major.

Experience

Utest – Freelance Quality Assurance Specialist (November 2022 – Until today)

UniAmerica

Planning and New Business Consultant (2016 - 2018)

- I led a team of 4 people, where my job was to ensure that each one of them was able to reach business goals.
- Monitor and analyze competitive actions, market monitoring, such as prices, products and trends.
- Implemented plans of short, medium and long term sales
 plans and strategies, aiming at meeting the goals established
 in terms of product mix, customer service, acting in all
 activities and solving complex problems.
- Logistics structuring of the business, and follow-up from the start until the delivery of the product.
- Seek the growth of the market share through innovations / adaptations of products and processes with high added value.
- Monitor the fluctuations in gross product margins, suggesting and /or adopting measures to maintain profitability.
- Search and implement solutions that meet the demands of each client, interacting with the technical area / laboratory.

TETO (TECHO)

Volunteer work (2015 – 2016)

 As a Volunteer I worked in several favelas in São Paulo. Bringing food to needy families, and often helping to build new homes for families who lost everything in landslides, helping with renovations to homes in a precarious situation.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

QA Software Tester

Technion - Institute of Technology (May 2022–November 2022)

Fault management systems: JIRA and MONDAY

Languages: Familiarity with HTML CSS and also with JAVA at a

basic level

Automation: working with SELENIUM

Databases: advanced level SQL, knowledge of queries up to the JOIN level including grouping commands and subqueries

Test documents: experience in writing STP/STD/STR documents

- full projects

Management in TESTRAIL software

International Business

Anhembi Morumbi University (2016 – 2018)

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- People management Getulio Vargas Foundation (2016)
- Sales Techniques
 School of Advertising and Marketing (2017)
- Basic Human Resources Getulio Vargas Foundation (2016)
- Basic Finance Entrepreneurs Endeavor Entrepreneurship (2016)